<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MyJournal</title>
    <description>&lt;h3&gt;Hello world, this is&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h1&gt;MyJournal&lt;/h1&gt;</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:29:17 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:29:17 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>First post on my blog to test everything's working properly.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just writing this to test everything’s working fine. You probably, already know what to expect from this post because you have already read the title. But anyway, I have to continue writing until it’s about 3-4 lines so that I get a rough understanding how things look. I have already tested this, of course but this will be a test on production site and I don’t want to add Lorem ipsom. Uh, I guess that should be enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me also try a tiny JS snippet. Hope that works out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-js&quot; data-lang=&quot;js&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kd&quot;&gt;var&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;newVar&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Log this: &quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;+&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;newVar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, it did work properly. I am glad it worked. As you can see, it’s a last day of 2018. I have so much to write about 2018; but not right now. I have to host this site now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 16:25:20 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/update/2018/12/31/testing-things.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/update/2018/12/31/testing-things.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Present is a present</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s almost 21:00; I have a semester exam at 14:00, tomorrow. As usual, I haven’t studied anything yet. Although, I still hope that I will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this very moment, I am thinking - how did this happen? I mean, I had so much time. I was ready t..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An alarm rang;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It reminded me about one of my friend’s birthday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked up my guitar, recorded ‘Happy birthday’ - so that I can wish him at exact 12AM. But I have to calculate - when exactly to press that ‘send’ button(?) I want mine to be the first wish. Okay, the file size is about 3MB; Based on my Internet (upload)speed, it takes at least 2 minutes(3G but, yeah). So, I have to tap send button at 23:58.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Ok Google, remind me to wish my friend at 11 58.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Ok, do you want to save this?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Yes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I heard my recording twice to make sure it’s good enough to send. Heard that one more time to appreciate myself. And yet, I tried one more time just to see whether I can do any better. Heard the new one twice but I decided to stick with the first the attempt. Scrolled down to see a lot of old-buried recordings which I had almost forgotten. Stuck my headphones, and played a random recording. Suddenly I realized, I have exam tomorrow! Surprisingly, it was just 21:20. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;Oh cool, let me hear just this one and then I will study&quot;&lt;/code&gt; And when I glanced at the time a few minutes later, it was 22:00. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;Shit!!&quot;&lt;/code&gt; I took my pen and started planning what to study. But deep inside, I was not happy about that time-calculation I made about ‘when’ to send that recording. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;Ohhh, yeah, I didn't consider his downloading time! How can I forget that?? Damn! So, I know he has 3G; It takes 10-15 seconds to download. So, my planning is okay but a minute earlier would be much better.&quot;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;em&gt;Changed the reminder manually&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;But wait, this is exam time; What if he turned off his cell phone/data(?). Wait, let me text him now and see.&quot;&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;Damn, he is offline; Let me call him and ask for study suggestion and to come online, too! :)&quot;.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[calling…]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[still calling…]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Him:&lt;/strong&gt; “Hello(..?)”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Me:&lt;/strong&gt; “En madakattile?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Odakattin le; Barobbari haryakatteti subject!”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Uhhm.. okay. Yav yav chapter odakatti?”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“1, 2, 4, 7, 8”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“3, 5, 6??!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Av doddv adav. Nee yav odakatti?”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Uh, naanu 1, 2, 4, 7, 8 odakatteni”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Oh okay..”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Important question yavara list maadi?”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Hu le, 1st chapter, 2nd chapter matt 8th valag predictable adav.”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Nang questions kalas avann, what’s-app naag”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Barko le pa; Nannkade net illa”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Crap!&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Okay hel pa”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;hr /&gt;
  &lt;hr /&gt;
  &lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“So, ivasht important?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Haa, ivv baru chance aiti naale.. nee en, eeg odak kunti en?”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“hu le pa”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Gottaittogopa; Hinga andd andd score madtiri.”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Yappa elli score o maraya! By the way, advance happy birthday le”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Ae thanks le. Nenap ittiyapa exam time naagu?”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;I hated my cell phone for reminding me.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Hu le; aat tago pa.. od; Naale bhetti aaguna”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Okay le, Bye”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Bye.”;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This happened exactly 11 years ago..in binary. I don’t know where he is now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Found those recordings today, this time, I liked the second attempt. He never heard it, though. Perhaps, he never will. I had spent about 20 minutes of my time making them and perfecting them. Perhaps, it was just meant to be an experience for myself to reflect upon - only time can tell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Now, I am gonna start this article with the word now. Oh, I already did. Anyway, now that I am 3 years in the future, what I would like to say to my past self if I ever get to meet him?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
First thing, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;You are stupid. Period&quot;&lt;/code&gt;;
Second, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;You waste too much time thinking about useless things!&quot;&lt;/code&gt;
Third, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;You never thought about circumstances. You acted blindly. You are such a boring person.&quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
He replied!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Okay. Maybe you are smarter than me. I agree that I did think about useless things which are no longer useful to you now. I did act blindly time to time because, as you said, I am stupid compared to you. But hey, you are what you are because of me. All those useless thoughts made you what you are today. You know those are useless because you spent time thinking about them. At a subconscious level, they defined you. It makes perfect sense to you now, right? There is no you without me. It sounds cliche, but it’s true and you know it. Yes, I’ve made many mistakes but I did some really good things too; I know you are proud of them still. And about those mistakes, how well are you doing on them now? You can’t blame me for what I was. Because you are the result of me. I defined you, man. You know, if you think about it, I was way cooler than you. I had time to play guitar, play TT, study philosophy and many more things. What do you do these days? I don’t see much playfulness in your life these days. Again, sounds cliche. But you know what I mean. Seems like you’ve lost your freedom growing up. Sorry, but I almost wanna laugh at you, man.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Okay, I had forgotten that you were egoistic, too. But.. yeah, you are right about many things. Do you remember, once you wrote something like ‘Present is indeed present’ and tried to make sense of it but it went tough? Guess what, I haven’t figured it out yet. Maybe that’s why I am still thinking about you. Truly, thank you for everything you’ve done for present-me. In a way, you’ve gifted me my present self. Thank you. Present is truly a present.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;!-- You might have a million dollar idea. But it worths nothing if you don't live right now. --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.melinaabbott.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/free-gift.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;present&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 20:47:20 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/update/2016/06/22/present-is-present.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/update/2016/06/22/present-is-present.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
